[
    {
        "qid": 64748,
        "question": "Patient is a 43 year old female.<br>- The patient has felt confused or disorientated lately.<br>- The patient has been in contact with a person with similar symptoms in the past 2 weeks.<br>- The patient has had diarrhea or an increase in stool frequency.<br>- The patient has been in contact with someone infected with the Ebola virus in the last month.<br>- The patient constantly feels fatigued or has non-restful sleep.<br>- The patient has diffuse (widespread) muscle pain.<br>- The patient has noticed unusual bleeding or bruising related to their consultation today.<br>- The patient has a cough.<br>- The patient has traveled to West Africa in the last 4 weeks.",
        "option1": "Pancreatic neoplasm",
        "option2": "Bronchitis",
        "option3": "Anemia",
        "option4": "Ebola",
        "correct_option": 4,
        "ai_prediction": 4,
        "ai_confidence": "76%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": 82633,
        "question": "Patient is a 0 year old female.<br>- The patient has recently had a viral infection.<br>- The patient has pain somewhere, related to their reason for consulting.<br>- The patient's pain is sensitive.<br>- The patient feels pain on the right side of the chest, the left side of the chest, and the right breast.<br>- The intensity of the patient's pain is 4 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain does not radiate to another location.<br>- The pain is precisely located at a level of 7 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain appeared at a speed of 1 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient feels out of breath with minimal physical effort.<br>- The patient is experiencing shortness of breath or difficulty breathing in a significant way.<br>- The patient has not traveled out of the country in the last 4 weeks.<br>- The patient has symptoms that are increased with physical exertion but alleviated with rest.",
        "option1": "Myocarditis",
        "option2": "Systemic lupus erythematosus (SLE)",
        "option3": "Chagas",
        "option4": "Scombroid food poisoning",
        "correct_option": 1,
        "ai_prediction": 1,
        "ai_confidence": "90%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": 29980,
        "question": "Patient is a 12 year old female.<br>- The patient has pain somewhere, related to their reason for consulting.<br>- The patient's pain is heartbreaking.<br>- The patient feels pain in the lower chest, right flank, upper chest, belly, and epigastric region.<br>- The intensity of the patient's pain is 10 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain radiates to the thoracic spine and left scapula.<br>- The pain is located with a precision of 6 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain appeared at a speed of 9 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient is feeling nauseous or feels like vomiting.<br>- The patient has not traveled out of the country in the last 4 weeks.<br>- The patient has vomited several times or has made several efforts to vomit.",
        "option1": "Boerhaave",
        "option2": "Anaphylaxis",
        "option3": "Chagas",
        "option4": "Pericarditis",
        "correct_option": 1,
        "ai_prediction": 1,
        "ai_confidence": "78%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": 238885,
        "question": "Patient is a 16 year old male.<br>- The patient has pain somewhere, related to their reason for consulting.<br>- The patient's pain is sensitive and burning.<br>- The patient feels pain in the left breast, the right posterior chest wall, and the left posterior chest wall.<br>- The patient's pain intensity is 5 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain does not radiate to another location.<br>- The pain is precisely located at a level of 7 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain appeared at a speed of 4 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient has a sore throat.<br>- The patient has a chronic obstructive pulmonary disease (COPD).<br>- The patient has a cough.<br>- The patient has not traveled out of the country in the last 4 weeks.<br>- The patient's vaccinations are up to date.<br>- The patient has noticed a wheezing sound when they exhale.",
        "option1": "Upper respiratory tract infection (URTI)",
        "option2": "Scombroid food poisoning",
        "option3": "Anaphylaxis",
        "option4": "Bronchitis",
        "correct_option": 4,
        "ai_prediction": 4,
        "ai_confidence": "90%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": 415813,
        "question": "Patient is a 17 year old female.<br>- The patient has pain somewhere, related to their reason for consulting.<br>- The patient's pain is heartbreaking, haunting, like a knife stroke, and violent.<br>- The patient feels pain in the lower chest, left flank, upper chest, right hypochondrium, and epigastric region.<br>- The patient's pain intensity is 6 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain radiates to the thoracic spine and the right scapula.<br>- The patient's pain is precisely located at a level of 3 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain appeared at a speed of 7 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient drinks alcohol excessively or has an addiction to alcohol.<br>- The patient is feeling nauseous and feels like vomiting.<br>- The patient has not traveled out of the country in the last 4 weeks.<br>- The patient has vomited several times or has made several efforts to vomit.",
        "option1": "Chagas",
        "option2": "Boerhaave",
        "option3": "Scombroid food poisoning",
        "option4": "Anaphylaxis",
        "correct_option": 2,
        "ai_prediction": 2,
        "ai_confidence": "50%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": 956276,
        "question": "Patient is a 0 year old female.<br>- The patient has pain somewhere, related to their reason for consulting.<br>- The patient's pain is sensitive.<br>- The patient feels pain in the lower chest, the right side of the chest, the right breast, and the left breast.<br>- The intensity of the patient's pain is 3 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain does not radiate to another location.<br>- The pain is precisely located at a level of 4 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain appeared at a speed of 0 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient feels out of breath with minimal physical effort.<br>- The patient is experiencing shortness of breath or difficulty breathing in a significant way.<br>- The patient feels their heart is beating fast, irregularly, or they feel palpitations.<br>- The patient has not traveled out of the country in the last 4 weeks.<br>- The patient's symptoms are worse when lying down and alleviated while sitting up.",
        "option1": "Chagas",
        "option2": "Myocarditis",
        "option3": "Gastroesophageal reflux disease (GERD)",
        "option4": "Sarcoidosis",
        "correct_option": 2,
        "ai_prediction": 3,
        "ai_confidence": "53%",
        "ai_is_correct": false
    },
    {
        "qid": 254814,
        "question": "Patient is a 61 year old male.<br>- The patient feels anxious.<br>- The patient regularly drinks coffee or tea.<br>- The patient has pain somewhere, related to their reason for consulting.<br>- The patient's pain is burning.<br>- The patient feels pain at the top of the head.<br>- The intensity of the patient's pain is 5 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain does not radiate to another location.<br>- The pain is precisely located at a level of 7 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain appeared at a speed of 7 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient feels slightly dizzy or lightheaded.<br>- The patient feels their heart is beating fast, irregularly, or they feel palpitations.<br>- The patient has not traveled out of the country in the last 4 weeks.",
        "option1": "Chagas",
        "option2": "HIV (initial infection)",
        "option3": "Anemia",
        "option4": "Paroxysmal supraventricular tachycardia (PSVT)",
        "correct_option": 4,
        "ai_prediction": 4,
        "ai_confidence": "79%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": 90600,
        "question": "Patient is a 41 year old male.<br>- The patient has a poor diet.<br>- The patient has had a diagnosis of anemia.<br>- The patient has family members who have been diagnosed with anemia.<br>- The patient has pain somewhere, related to their reason for consulting.<br>- The patient's pain is characterized as a cramp.<br>- The patient feels pain in the right temple and left temple.<br>- The intensity of the patient's pain is 2 on a scale of 0 to 10.<br>- The patient's pain does not radiate to another location.<br>- The pain is precisely located at a level of 6 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain appeared at a speed of 1 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient feels slightly dizzy or lightheaded.<br>- The patient feels lightheaded and dizzy or feels like they are about to faint.<br>- The patient feels so tired that they are unable to do their usual activities or are stuck in bed all day long.<br>- The patient has chronic kidney failure.<br>- The patient has recently had stools that were black, like coal.<br>- The patient is taking new oral anticoagulants (NOACs).<br>- The patient's skin is much paler than usual.<br>- The patient has noticed light red blood or blood clots in their stool.<br>- The patient has traveled to Asia in the last 4 weeks.<br>- The patient's BMI is less than 18.5, indicating they are underweight.",
        "option1": "Paroxysmal supraventricular tachycardia (PSVT)",
        "option2": "Atrial fibrillation",
        "option3": "Cluster headache",
        "option4": "Anemia",
        "correct_option": 4,
        "ai_prediction": 4,
        "ai_confidence": "52%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": 1022703,
        "question": "Patient is a 0 year old male.<br>- The patient does not feel pain anywhere.<br>- The patient has a fever, either felt or measured with a thermometer.<br>- The patient has been more irritable or their mood has been very unstable recently.<br>- The patient has nasal congestion or a clear runny nose.<br>- The patient has not traveled out of the country in the last 4 weeks.",
        "option1": "Upper respiratory tract infection (URTI)",
        "option2": "Croup",
        "option3": "Chagas",
        "option4": "Acute otitis media",
        "correct_option": 4,
        "ai_prediction": 4,
        "ai_confidence": "69%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": 368735,
        "question": "Patient is a 55 year old male.<br>- The patient has had a diagnosis of anemia.<br>- The patient has family members who have been diagnosed with anemia.<br>- The patient has pain somewhere, related to their reason for consulting.<br>- The patient's pain is tugging.<br>- The patient feels pain at the back of the head, top of the head, right temple, and left temple.<br>- The patient's pain intensity is 2 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain does not radiate to another location.<br>- The pain is precisely located at a level of 3 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain appeared at a speed of 5 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient feels lightheaded and dizzy or feels like they are about to faint.<br>- The patient constantly feels fatigued or has non-restful sleep.<br>- The patient has chronic kidney failure.<br>- The patient is taking new oral anticoagulants (NOACs).<br>- The patient has traveled to Central America in the last 4 weeks.<br>- The patient's BMI is less than 18.5, indicating they are underweight.",
        "option1": "Possible NSTEMI / STEMI",
        "option2": "Scombroid food poisoning",
        "option3": "Anemia",
        "option4": "Cluster headache",
        "correct_option": 3,
        "ai_prediction": 1,
        "ai_confidence": "43%",
        "ai_is_correct": false
    },
    {
        "qid": 529822,
        "question": "Patient is a 63 year old male.<br>- The patient regularly drinks coffee or tea.<br>- The patient does not feel pain anywhere.<br>- The patient feels lightheaded and dizzy or feels like they are about to faint.<br>- The patient feels their heart is beating fast, irregularly, or they feel palpitations.<br>- The patient has not traveled out of the country in the last 4 weeks.",
        "option1": "Panic attack",
        "option2": "Anemia",
        "option3": "Scombroid food poisoning",
        "option4": "Paroxysmal supraventricular tachycardia (PSVT)",
        "correct_option": 4,
        "ai_prediction": 4,
        "ai_confidence": "65%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": 453793,
        "question": "Patient is a 4 year old female.<br>- The patient has been in contact with a person with similar symptoms in the past 2 weeks.<br>- The patient attends or works in a daycare.<br>- The patient has pain somewhere, related to their reason for consulting.<br>- The patient's pain is sensitive and burning.<br>- The patient feels pain in the right tonsil, left tonsil, thyroid cartilage, palate, and pharynx.<br>- The intensity of the patient's pain is 6 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain does not radiate to another location.<br>- The pain is precisely located at a level of 8 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain appeared at a speed of 4 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient smokes cigarettes.<br>- The patient has a fever, either felt or measured with a thermometer.<br>- The patient has nasal congestion or a clear runny nose.<br>- The patient has traveled to North America in the last 4 weeks.<br>- The patient is immunosuppressed.",
        "option1": "Viral pharyngitis",
        "option2": "Croup",
        "option3": "Upper respiratory tract infection (URTI)",
        "option4": "Acute laryngitis",
        "correct_option": 1,
        "ai_prediction": 1,
        "ai_confidence": "68%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": 681664,
        "question": "Patient is a 17 year old male.<br>- The patient has pain somewhere, related to their reason for consulting.<br>- The patient's pain is sensitive.<br>- The patient feels pain in the right breast, left breast, and right posterior chest wall.<br>- The intensity of the patient's pain is 4 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain does not radiate to another location.<br>- The pain is precisely located at a level of 3 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain appeared at a speed of 0 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient has a sore throat.<br>- The patient has chronic obstructive pulmonary disease (COPD).<br>- The patient has a cough.<br>- The patient has not traveled out of the country in the last 4 weeks.<br>- The patient has noticed a wheezing sound when they exhale.",
        "option1": "Upper respiratory tract infection (URTI)",
        "option2": "Bronchitis",
        "option3": "Anaphylaxis",
        "option4": "Scombroid food poisoning",
        "correct_option": 2,
        "ai_prediction": 2,
        "ai_confidence": "71%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": 448598,
        "question": "Patient is a 54 year old male.<br>- The patient has had diarrhea or an increase in stool frequency.<br>- The patient has been in contact with someone infected with the Ebola virus in the last month.<br>- The patient constantly feels fatigued or has non-restful sleep.<br>- The patient has a sore throat.<br>- The patient has noticed unusual bleeding or bruising related to their consultation today.<br>- The patient has a cough.<br>- The patient has traveled to West Africa in the last 4 weeks.",
        "option1": "Bronchitis",
        "option2": "Anemia",
        "option3": "Ebola",
        "option4": "Pancreatic neoplasm",
        "correct_option": 3,
        "ai_prediction": 3,
        "ai_confidence": "81%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": 81807,
        "question": "Patient is a 29 year old male.<br>- The patient feels anxious.<br>- The patient regularly drinks coffee or tea.<br>- The patient does not feel pain anywhere.<br>- The patient consumes energy drinks regularly.<br>- The patient feels slightly dizzy or lightheaded.<br>- The patient feels that their heart is beating fast (racing), irregularly (missing a beat), or they feel palpitations.<br>- The patient has not traveled out of the country in the last 4 weeks.<br>- The patient has recently taken decongestants or other substances that may have stimulant effects.",
        "option1": "Paroxysmal supraventricular tachycardia (PSVT)",
        "option2": "Anemia",
        "option3": "Atrial fibrillation",
        "option4": "Scombroid food poisoning",
        "correct_option": 1,
        "ai_prediction": 1,
        "ai_confidence": "53%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    }
]